<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PrivSet</string>
    <string name="admob_app_id">ADMOB_APP_ID</string>
    <string name="interstitial_ad_unit_id">INTERSTITIAL_AD_ID</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">BANNER_AD_ID1</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id2">BANNER_AD_ID2</string>

<string name="config_freeformWindowManagement">
 The device supports freeform window management. Windows have title bars and can be moved
         and resized. If you set this to true, you also need to add
         PackageManager.FEATURE_FREEFORM_WINDOW_MANAGEMENT feature to your device specification.
         The duplication is necessary, because this information is used before the features are
         available to the system.
</string>
<string name="config_backPanicBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user panic presses the back button.
   0 - Nothing
   1 - Go to home
</string>
<string name="config_supportsMultiWindow">
 True if the device supports at least one form of multi-window.
         E.g. freeform, split-screen, picture-in-picture.
</string>
<string name="config_useRoundIcon">
 Flag indicating whether round icons should be parsed from the application manifest.
</string>
<string name="config_supportSystemNavigationKeys">
 True if the device supports system navigation keys.
</string>
<string name="config_sf_limitedAlpha">
 Flag indicating whether the surface flinger has limited
         alpha compositing functionality in hardware.  If set, the window
         manager will disable alpha trasformation in animations where not
         strictly needed
</string>
<string name="ImsConnectedDefaultValue">
 Default value used to block data calls if ims is not
         connected.  If you use the ims apn DCT will block
         any other apn from connecting until ims apn is connected
</string>
<string name="config_sf_slowBlur">
 Flag indicating whether the surface flinger is inefficient
         at performing a blur.  Used by parts of the UI to turn off
         the blur effect where it isn\'t worth the performance hit.
         As of Honeycomb, blurring is not supported anymore.
</string>
<string name="config_useVolumeKeySounds">
 Flag indicating that the media framework should support playing of sounds on volume
         key usage.  This adds noticeable additional overhead to volume key processing, so
         is disableable for products for which it is irrelevant.
</string>
<string name="config_soundEffectVolumeDb">
 The attenuation in dB applied to the sound effects played
         through AudioManager.playSoundEffect() when no volume is specified.
</string>
<string name="config_lockSoundVolumeDb">
 The attenuation in dB applied to the lock/unlock sounds.
</string>
<string name="config_sendAudioBecomingNoisy">
 Flag indicating whether the AUDIO_BECOMING_NOISY notification should
         be sent during a change to the audio output device.
</string>
<string name="config_shortAnimTime">
 The duration (in milliseconds) of a short animation.
</string>
<string name="config_mediumAnimTime">
 The duration (in milliseconds) of a medium-length animation.
</string>
<string name="config_longAnimTime">
 The duration (in milliseconds) of a long animation.
</string>
<string name="config_activityShortDur">
 The duration (in milliseconds) of the activity open/close and fragment open/close animations.
</string>
    <string name="config_activityDefaultDur">
 The duration (in milliseconds) of the activity open/close and fragment open/close animations.
</string>
<string name="config_ui_enableFadingMarquee">
 Enables or disables fading edges when marquee is enabled in TextView.
         Off by default, since the framebuffer readback used to implement the
         fading edges is prohibitively expensive on most GPUs.
</string>
<string name="config_closeDialogWhenTouchOutside">
 Whether dialogs should close automatically when the user touches outside
         of them.  This should not normally be modified.
</string>
<string name="config_avoidGfxAccel">
 Device configuration indicating whether we should avoid using accelerated graphics
         in certain places to reduce RAM footprint.  This is ignored if ro.config.low_ram
         is true (in that case this is assumed true as well).  It can allow you to tune down
         your device\'s memory use without going to the point of causing applications to turn
         off features.
</string>
<string name="config_lowMemoryKillerMinFreeKbytesAbsolute">
 Device configuration setting the minfree tunable in the lowmemorykiller in the kernel.
         A high value will cause the lowmemorykiller to fire earlier, keeping more memory
         in the file cache and preventing I/O thrashing, but allowing fewer processes to
         stay in memory.  A low value will keep more processes in memory but may cause
         thrashing if set too low.  Overrides the default value chosen by ActivityManager
         based on screen size and total memory for the largest lowmemorykiller bucket, and
         scaled proportionally to the smaller buckets.  -1 keeps the default.
</string>
<string name="config_lowMemoryKillerMinFreeKbytesAdjust">
 Device configuration adjusting the minfree tunable in the lowmemorykiller in the
         kernel.  A high value will cause the lowmemorykiller to fire earlier, keeping more
         memory in the file cache and preventing I/O thrashing, but allowing fewer processes
         to stay in memory.  A low value will keep more processes in memory but may cause
         thrashing if set too low.  Directly added to the default value chosen by
         ActivityManager based on screen size and total memory for the largest lowmemorykiller
         bucket, and scaled proportionally to the smaller buckets. 0 keeps the default.
</string>
<string name="config_extraFreeKbytesAbsolute">
 Device configuration setting the /proc/sys/vm/extra_free_kbytes tunable in the kernel
         (if it exists).  A high value will increase the amount of memory that the kernel
         tries to keep free, reducing allocation time and causing the lowmemorykiller to kill
         earlier.  A low value allows more memory to be used by processes but may cause more
         allocations to block waiting on disk I/O or lowmemorykiller.  Overrides the default
         value chosen by ActivityManager based on screen size.  0 prevents keeping any extra
         memory over what the kernel keeps by default.  -1 keeps the default.
</string>
<string name="config_extraFreeKbytesAdjust">
 Device configuration adjusting the /proc/sys/vm/extra_free_kbytes tunable in the kernel
         (if it exists).  0 uses the default value chosen by ActivityManager.  A positive value
         will increase the amount of memory that the kernel tries to keep free, reducing
         allocation time and causing the lowmemorykiller to kill earlier.  A negative value
         allows more memory to be used by processes but may cause more allocations to block
         waiting on disk I/O or lowmemorykiller.  Directly added to the default value chosen by
         ActivityManager based on screen size.
</string>
<string name="config_enableAutoPowerModes">
 Set this to true to enable the platform\'s auto-power-save modes like doze and
         app standby.  These are not enabled by default because they require a standard
         cloud-to-device messaging service for apps to interact correctly with the modes
         (such as to be able to deliver an instant message to the device even when it is
         dozing).  This should be enabled if you have such services and expect apps to
         correctly use them when installed on your device.  Otherwise, keep this disabled
         so that applications can still use their own mechanisms.
</string>
<string name="config_radioScanningTimeout">
 The duration (in milliseconds) that the radio will scan for a signal
         when there\'s no network connection. If the scan doesn\'t timeout, use zero
</string>
<string name="config_networkTransitionTimeout">
 The maximum duration (in milliseconds) we expect a network transition to take
</string>
<string name="config_automatic_brightness_available">
 Flag indicating whether the we should enable the automatic brightness in Settings.
         Software implementation will be used if config_hardware_auto_brightness_available is not set
</string>
<string name="config_annoy_dianne">
 Don\'t name config resources like this.  It should look like config_annoyDianne
</string>
<string name="config_unplugTurnsOnScreen">
 If this is true, the screen will come on when you unplug usb/power/whatever.
</string>
<string name="config_useAttentionLight">
 Set this true only if the device has separate attention and notification lights.
</string>
<string name="config_animateScreenLights">
 If this is true, the screen will fade off.
</string>
<string name="config_enableScreenshotChord">
 If this is true, key chords can be used to take a screenshot on the device.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromUnplug">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode when plugged in or unplugged.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromGesture">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from gesture.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromCameraLens">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from camera lens cover is switched.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromPowerKey">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from power key press.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromKey">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from regular key press. Setting this value to
         true implies config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromPowerKey is also true
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromMotion">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from motion.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromMotionWhenNotDreaming">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from motion.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromLidSwitch">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from lid switch.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromDock">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode when docked.
</string>
<string name="config_allowTheaterModeWakeFromWindowLayout">
 If this is true, allow wake from theater mode from window layout flag.
</string>
<string name="config_goToSleepOnButtonPressTheaterMode">
 If this is true, go to sleep when theater mode is enabled from button press
</string>
<string name="config_supportLongPressPowerWhenNonInteractive">
 If this is true, long press on power button will be available from the non-interactive state
</string>
<string name="config_supportAutoRotation">
 If true, enables auto-rotation features using the accelerometer.
         Otherwise, auto-rotation is disabled.  Applications may still request
         to use specific orientations but the sensor is ignored and sensor-based
         orientations are not available.  Furthermore, all auto-rotation related
         settings are omitted from the system UI.  In certain situations we may
         still use the accelerometer to determine the orientation, such as when
         docked if the dock is configured to enable the accelerometer.
</string>
<string name="config_allowAllRotations">
 If true, the screen can be rotated via the accelerometer in all 4
         rotations as the default behavior.
</string>
<string name="config_reverseDefaultRotation">
 If true, the direction rotation is applied to get to an application\'s requested
         orientation is reversed.  Normally, the model is that landscape is
         clockwise from portrait; thus on a portrait device an app requesting
         landscape will cause a clockwise rotation, and on a landscape device an
         app requesting portrait will cause a counter-clockwise rotation.  Setting
         true here reverses that logic.
</string>
<string name="config_lidOpenRotation">
 The number of degrees to rotate the display when the keyboard is open.
         A value of -1 means no change in orientation by default.
</string>
<string name="config_lidKeyboardAccessibility">
 Indicate whether the lid state impacts the accessibility of
         the physical keyboard.  0 means it doesn\'t, 1 means it is accessible
         when the lid is open, 2 means it is accessible when the lid is
         closed.  The default is 0.
</string>
<string name="config_lidNavigationAccessibility">
 Indicate whether the lid state impacts the accessibility of
         the navigation buttons.  0 means it doesn\'t, 1 means it is accessible
         when the lid is open, 2 means it is accessible when the lid is
         closed.  The default is 0.
</string>
<string name="config_lidControlsSleep">
 Indicate whether closing the lid causes the device to go to sleep and opening
         it causes the device to wake up.
         The default is false.
</string>
<string name="config_deskDockRotation">
 The number of degrees to rotate the display when the device is in a desk dock.
         A value of -1 means no change in orientation by default.
</string>
<string name="config_deskDockKeepsScreenOn">
 Control whether being in the desk dock (and powered) always
         keeps the screen on.  By default it stays on when plugged in to
         AC.  0 will not keep it on; or together 1 to stay on when plugged
         in to AC and 2 to stay on when plugged in to USB.  (So 3 for both.)
</string>
<string name="config_deskDockEnablesAccelerometer">
 Control whether being in the desk dock should enable accelerometer
         based screen orientation.  This defaults to true because it is
         common for desk docks to be sold in a variety of form factors
         with different orientations.  Since we cannot always tell these docks
         apart and the docks cannot report their true orientation on their own,
         we rely on gravity to determine the effective orientation.
</string>
<string name="config_carDockRotation">
 The number of degrees to rotate the display when the device is in a car dock.
         A value of -1 means no change in orientation by default.
</string>
<string name="config_carDockKeepsScreenOn">
 Control whether being in the car dock (and powered) always
         keeps the screen on.  By default it stays on when plugged in to
         AC.  0 will not keep it on; or together 1 to stay on when plugged
         in to AC and 2 to stay on when plugged in to USB.  (So 3 for both.)
</string>
<string name="config_carDockEnablesAccelerometer">
 Control whether being in the car dock should enable accelerometer based
         screen orientation.  This defaults to true because putting a device in
         a car dock make the accelerometer more a physical input (like a lid).
</string>
<string name="config_undockedHdmiRotation">
 The number of degrees to rotate the display when the device has HDMI connected
         but is not in a dock.  A value of -1 means no change in orientation by default.
         Use -1 except on older devices whose Hardware Composer HAL does not
         provide full support for multiple displays.
</string>
<string name="config_defaultUiModeType">
 Control the default UI mode type to use when there is no other type override
         happening.  One of the following values (See Configuration.java):
             1  UI_MODE_TYPE_NORMAL
             4  UI_MODE_TYPE_TELEVISION
             5  UI_MODE_TYPE_APPLIANCE
             6  UI_MODE_TYPE_WATCH
         Any other values will have surprising consequences.
</string>
<string name="config_defaultNightMode">
 Control the default night mode to use when there is no other mode override set.
         One of the following values (see UiModeManager.java):
             0 - MODE_NIGHT_AUTO
             1 - MODE_NIGHT_NO
             2 - MODE_NIGHT_YES
</string>
<string name="config_suspendWhenScreenOffDueToProximity">
 Indicate whether to allow the device to suspend when the screen is off
         due to the proximity sensor.  This resource should only be set to true
         if the sensor HAL correctly handles the proximity sensor as a wake-up source.
         Otherwise, the device may fail to wake out of suspend reliably.
         The default is false.
</string>
<string name="config_longPressOnBackBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user long presses the back button.  Non-zero values are only
         valid for watches as part of CDD/CTS.
            0 - Nothing
            1 - Go to voice assist
</string>
<string name="config_longPressOnPowerBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user long presses the power button.
            0 - Nothing
            1 - Global actions menu
            2 - Power off (with confirmation)
            3 - Power off (without confirmation)
</string>
<string name="config_shortPressOnPowerBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user short presses the power button.
            0 - Nothing
            1 - Go to sleep (doze)
            2 - Really go to sleep (don\'t doze)
            3 - Really go to sleep and go home (don\'t doze)
</string>
<string name="config_doublePressOnPowerBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user double presses the power button.
            0 - Nothing
            1 - Toggle theater mode setting
            2 - Brightness boost
</string>
<string name="config_triplePressOnPowerBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user triple presses the power button.
            0 - Nothing
            1 - Toggle theater mode setting
            2 - Brightness boost
</string>
<string name="config_shortPressOnSleepBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user presses the sleep button.
            0 - Go to sleep (doze)
            1 - Go to sleep (doze) and go home
</string>
<string name="config_batterySdCardAccessibility">
 Indicate whether the SD card is accessible without removing the battery.
</string>
    <string name="config_use_strict_phone_number_comparation">

</string>
<string name="config_criticalBatteryWarningLevel">
 Display low battery warning when battery level dips to this value.
         Also, the battery stats are flushed to disk when we hit this level.
</string>
<string name="config_shutdownBatteryTemperature">
 Shutdown if the battery temperature exceeds (this value * 0.1) Celsius.
</string>
<string name="config_lowBatteryWarningLevel">
 Display low battery warning when battery level dips to this value
</string>
<string name="config_lowBatteryCloseWarningBump">
 Close low battery warning when battery level reaches the lowBatteryWarningLevel
         plus this
</string>
<string name="config_defaultNotificationColor">
 Default color for notification LED.
</string>
<string name="config_defaultNotificationLedOn">
 Default LED on time for notification LED in milliseconds.
</string>
<string name="config_defaultNotificationLedOff">
 Default LED off time for notification LED in milliseconds.
</string>
<string name="config_notificationsBatteryLowARGB">
 Default value for led color when battery is low on charge
</string>
<string name="config_notificationsBatteryMediumARGB">
 Default value for led color when battery is medium charged
</string>
<string name="config_notificationsBatteryFullARGB">
 Default value for led color when battery is fully charged
</string>
<string name="config_notificationsBatteryLedOn">
 Default value for LED on time when the battery is low on charge in miliseconds
</string>
<string name="config_intrusiveNotificationLed">
 Is the notification LED intrusive? Used to decide if there should be a disable option
</string>
<string name="config_notificationsBatteryLedOff">
 Default value for LED off time when the battery is low on charge in miliseconds
</string>
<string name="config_notificationServiceArchiveSize">
 Number of notifications to keep in the notification service historical archive
</string>
<string name="config_disableMenuKeyInLockScreen">
 Allow the menu hard key to be disabled in LockScreen on some devices
</string>
<string name="config_enableLockBeforeUnlockScreen">
 Don\'t show lock screen before unlock screen (PIN/pattern/password)
</string>
<string name="config_enableLockScreenRotation">
 Disable lockscreen rotation by default
</string>
<string name="config_enableLockScreenTranslucentDecor">
 Enable lockscreen translucent decor by default
</string>
<string name="config_enableTranslucentDecor">
 Enable translucent decor by default
</string>
<string name="config_hotswapCapable">
 Is the device capable of hot swapping an UICC Card
</string>
<string name="config_enable_puk_unlock_screen">
 Enable puk unlockscreen by default.
         If unlock screen is disabled, the puk should be unlocked through Emergency Dialer
</string>
<string name="config_enable_emergency_call_while_sim_locked">
 Enable emergency call when sim is locked or puk locked. Some countries/carriers do not
         allow emergency calls to be placed without the IMSI, which is locked in the SIM.
         If so, this should be set to \'false\' in an overlay.
</string>
<string name="config_longPressOnHomeBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user long presses the home button.
            0 - Nothing
            1 - Recent apps view in SystemUI
            2 - Launch assist intent
         This needs to match the constants in
         policy/src/com/android/internal/policy/impl/PhoneWindowManager.java
</string>
<string name="config_doubleTapOnHomeBehavior">
 Control the behavior when the user double-taps the home button.
            0 - Nothing
            1 - Recent apps view in SystemUI
         This needs to match the constants in
         policy/src/com/android/internal/policy/impl/PhoneWindowManager.java
</string>
<string name="config_screenBrightnessSettingMinimum">
 Minimum screen brightness setting allowed by the power manager.
         The user is forbidden from setting the brightness below this level.
</string>
<string name="config_screenBrightnessSettingMaximum">
 Maximum screen brightness allowed by the power manager.
         The user is forbidden from setting the brightness above this level.
</string>
<string name="config_screenBrightnessSettingDefault">
 Default screen brightness setting.
         Must be in the range specified by minimum and maximum.
</string>
<string name="config_screenBrightnessDoze">
 Screen brightness used to dim the screen while dozing in a very low power state.
         May be less than the minimum allowed brightness setting
         that can be set by the user.
</string>
<string name="config_allowAutoBrightnessWhileDozing">
 Allow automatic adjusting of the screen brightness while dozing in low power state.
</string>
<string name="config_autoBrightnessBrighteningLightDebounce">
 Stability requirements in milliseconds for accepting a new brightness level.  This is used
         for debouncing the light sensor.  Different constants are used to debounce the light sensor
         when adapting to brighter or darker environments.  This parameter controls how quickly
         brightness changes occur in response to an observed change in light level that exceeds the
         hysteresis threshold.
</string>
    <string name="config_autoBrightnessDarkeningLightDebounce">

</string>
<string name="config_autoBrightnessLightSensorRate">
 Light sensor event rate in milliseconds for automatic brightness control.
</string>
<string name="config_autoBrightnessResetAmbientLuxAfterWarmUp">
 When the screen is turned on, the previous estimate of the ambient light level at the time
         the screen was turned off is restored and is used to determine the initial screen
         brightness.
         If this flag is true, then the ambient light level estimate will be promptly recomputed
         after the warm-up interface and the screen brightness will be adjusted immediately.
         If this flag is false, then the ambient light level estimate will be adjusted more
         gradually in the same manner that normally happens when the screen is on according to the
         brightening or dimming debounce thresholds.  As a result, it may take somewhat longer to
         adapt to the environment.  This mode may be better suited for watches.
</string>
<string name="config_screenBrightnessDim">
 Screen brightness used to dim the screen when the user activity
         timeout expires.  May be less than the minimum allowed brightness setting
         that can be set by the user.
</string>
<string name="config_screenBrightnessDark">
 Minimum allowable screen brightness to use in a very dark room.
         This value sets the floor for the darkest possible auto-brightness
         adjustment.  It is expected to be somewhat less than the first entry in
         config_autoBrightnessLcdBacklightValues so as to allow the user to have
         some range of adjustment to dim the screen further than usual in very
         dark rooms. The contents of the screen must still be clearly visible
         in darkness (although they may not be visible in a bright room).
</string>
<string name="config_lightSensorWarmupTime">
 Amount of time it takes for the light sensor to warm up in milliseconds.
         For this time after the screen turns on, the Power Manager
         will not debounce light sensor readings
</string>
<string name="config_swipeDisambiguation">
 Enables swipe versus poly-finger touch disambiguation in the KeyboardView
</string>
<string name="config_virtualKeyQuietTimeMillis">
 Specifies the amount of time to disable virtual keys after the screen is touched
         in order to filter out accidental virtual key presses due to swiping gestures
         or taps near the edge of the display.  May be 0 to disable the feature.
         It is recommended that this value be no more than 250 ms.
         This feature should be disabled for most devices.
</string>
<string name="config_enableWallpaperService">
 True if WallpaperService is enabled
</string>
<string name="config_bluetooth_sco_off_call">
 Boolean indicating if current platform supports bluetooth SCO for off call
    use cases
</string>
<string name="config_bluetooth_wide_band_speech">
 Boolean indicating if current platform supports bluetooth wide band
         speech
</string>
<string name="config_bluetooth_address_validation">
 Boolean indicating if current platform need do one-time bluetooth address
         re-validation
</string>
<string name="config_bluetooth_le_peripheral_mode_supported">
 Boolean indicating if current platform supports BLE peripheral mode
</string>
<string name="config_datause_polling_period_sec">
 The default data-use polling period.
</string>
<string name="config_datause_threshold_bytes">
 The default data-use threshold in bytes. 0 disables
</string>
<string name="config_datause_throttle_kbitsps">
 The default reduced-datarate value in kilobits per sec
</string>
<string name="config_datause_notification_type">
 2 means give warning
</string>
<string name="config_volte_replacement_rat">
 If Voice Radio Technology is RIL_RADIO_TECHNOLOGY_LTE:14 or
         RIL_RADIO_TECHNOLOGY_UNKNOWN:0 this is the value that should be used instead.
         A configuration value of RIL_RADIO_TECHNOLOGY_UNKNOWN:0 means
         there is no replacement value and that the default assumption
         for phone type (GSM) should be used.
</string>
<string name="config_voice_capable">
 Flag indicating whether the current device is "voice capable".
         If true, this means that the device supports circuit-switched
         (i.e. voice) phone calls over the telephony network, and is
         allowed to display the in-call UI while a cellular voice call is
         active.  This can be overridden to false for "data only" devices
         which can\'t make voice calls and don\'t support any in-call UI.
         Note: this flag is subtly different from the
         PackageManager.FEATURE_TELEPHONY system feature, which is
         available on *any* device with a telephony radio, even if the
         device is data-only.
</string>
<string name="config_user_notification_of_restrictied_mobile_access">
 Flag indicating if the user is notified when the mobile network access is restricted
</string>
<string name="config_sms_capable">
 Flag indicating whether the current device allows sms service.
         If true, this means that the device supports both sending and
         receiving sms via the telephony network.
         This can be overridden to false for "data only" devices
         which can\'t send and receive sms message.
         Note: Disable SMS also disable voicemail waiting sms,
               cell broadcasting sms, and MMS.
</string>
<string name="config_bluetooth_default_profiles">
 Enable/disable default bluetooth profiles:
        HSP_AG, ObexObjectPush, Audio, NAP
</string>
<string name="config_sip_wifi_only">
 Enables SIP on WIFI only
</string>
<string name="config_built_in_sip_phone">
 Enables built-in SIP phone capability
</string>
<string name="db_connection_pool_size">
 Maximum number of database connections opened and managed by framework layer
         to handle queries on each database when using Write-Ahead Logging.
</string>
<string name="db_journal_size_limit">
 Maximum size of the persistent journal file in bytes.
         If the journal file grows to be larger than this amount then SQLite will
         truncate it after committing the transaction.
</string>
<string name="db_wal_autocheckpoint">
 The Write-Ahead Log auto-checkpoint interval in database pages (typically 1 to 4KB).
         The log is checkpointed automatically whenever it exceeds this many pages.
         When a database is reopened, its journal mode is set back to the default
         journal mode, which may cause a checkpoint operation to occur.  Checkpoints
         can also happen at other times when transactions are committed.
         The bigger the WAL file, the longer a checkpoint operation takes, so we try
         to keep the WAL file relatively small to avoid long delays.
         The size of the WAL file is also constrained by \'db_journal_size_limit\'.
</string>
<string name="config_downloadDataDirSize">
 Max space (in MB) allocated to DownloadManager to store the downloaded
         files if they are to be stored in DownloadManager\'s data dir,
         which typically is /data/data/com.android.providers.downloads/files
</string>
<string name="config_MaxConcurrentDownloadsAllowed">
 Max number of downloads allowed to proceed concurrently
</string>
<string name="config_downloadDataDirLowSpaceThreshold">
 When the free space available in DownloadManager\'s data dir falls
         below the percentage value specified by this param, DownloadManager
         starts removing files to try to make percentage of available
         free space above this threshold value.
</string>
<string name="config_cursorWindowSize">
 When a database query is executed, the results retuned are paginated
         in pages of size (in KB) indicated by this value
</string>
<string name="config_showMenuShortcutsWhenKeyboardPresent">
 Sets whether menu shortcuts should be displayed on panel menus when
         a keyboard is present.
</string>
<string name="config_telephony_use_own_number_for_voicemail">
 The VoiceMail default value is displayed to my own number if it is true
</string>
<string name="config_sms_utf8_support">
 If this value is true, Sms encoded as octet is decoded by utf8 decoder.
         If false, decoded by Latin decoder.
</string>
<string name="config_mms_content_disposition_support">
 If this value is true, The mms content-disposition field is supported correctly.
         If false, Content-disposition fragments are ignored
</string>
<string name="config_alwaysUseCdmaRssi">
 Set to true if the RSSI should always display CDMA signal strength even on EVDO
</string>
<string name="config_duplicate_port_omadm_wappush">
 If this value is true, duplicate Source/Destination port fields
         in WDP header of some carriers OMADM wap push are supported.
         ex: MSGTYPE-TotalSegments-CurrentSegment
             -SourcePortDestPort-SourcePortDestPort-OMADM PDU
         If false, not supported.
</string>
<string name="status_bar_notification_info_maxnum">
 Maximum numerical value that will be shown in a status bar
         notification icon or in the notification itself. Will be replaced
         with @string/status_bar_notification_info_overflow when shown in the
         UI.
</string>
<string name="config_showNavigationBar">
 Whether a software navigation bar should be shown. NOTE: in the future this may be
         autodetected from the Configuration.
</string>
<string name="config_actionMenuItemAllCaps">
 Whether action menu items should be displayed in ALLCAPS or not.
         Defaults to true. If this is not appropriate for specific locales
         it should be disabled in that locale\'s resources.
</string>
<string name="config_allowActionMenuItemTextWithIcon">
 Whether action menu items should obey the "withText" showAsAction
         flag. This may be set to false for situations where space is
         extremely limited.
</string>
<string name="config_ntpPollingInterval">
 Normal polling frequency in milliseconds
</string>
<string name="config_ntpPollingIntervalShorter">
 Try-again polling interval in milliseconds, in case the network request failed
</string>
<string name="config_ntpRetry">
 Number of times to try again with the shorter interval, before backing
         off until the normal polling interval. A value 0 indicates infinite.
</string>
<string name="config_ntpThreshold">
 If the time difference is greater than this threshold in milliseconds,
         then update the time.
</string>
<string name="config_ntpTimeout">
 Timeout to wait for NTP server response.
</string>
<string name="config_networkPolicyDefaultWarning">
 Default network policy warning threshold, in megabytes.
</string>
<string name="config_wimaxEnabled">
 Set and Unsets WiMAX
</string>
<string name="config_dreamsSupported">
 Specifies whether the dreams feature should be supported.
         When true, the system will allow the user to configure dreams (screensavers)
         to launch when a user activity timeout occurs or the system is told to nap.
         When false, the dreams feature will be disabled (this does not affect dozing).
         Consider setting this resource to false or disabling dreams by default when a
         doze component is specified below since dreaming will supercede dozing and
         will prevent the system from entering a low power state until the dream ends.
</string>
<string name="config_dreamsEnabledByDefault">
 If supported, are dreams enabled? (by default)
</string>
<string name="config_dreamsActivatedOnDockByDefault">
 If supported and enabled, are dreams activated when docked? (by default)
</string>
<string name="config_dreamsActivatedOnSleepByDefault">
 If supported and enabled, are dreams activated when asleep and charging? (by default)
</string>
<string name="config_dreamsEnabledOnBattery">
 Are we allowed to dream while not plugged in?
</string>
<string name="config_dreamsBatteryLevelMinimumWhenPowered">
 Minimum battery level to allow dreaming when powered.
         Use -1 to disable this safety feature.
</string>
<string name="config_dreamsBatteryLevelMinimumWhenNotPowered">
 Minimum battery level to allow dreaming when not powered.
         Use -1 to disable this safety feature.
</string>
<string name="config_dreamsBatteryLevelDrainCutoff">
 If the battery level drops by this percentage and the user activity timeout
         has expired, then assume the device is receiving insufficient current to charge
         effectively and terminate the dream.  Use -1 to disable this safety feature.
</string>
<string name="config_dozeAfterScreenOff">
 If true, the doze component is not started until after the screen has been
         turned off and the screen off animation has been performed.
</string>
<string name="config_powerDecoupleAutoSuspendModeFromDisplay">
 Power Management: Specifies whether to decouple the auto-suspend state of the
         device from the display on/off state.
         When false, autosuspend_disable() will be called before the display is turned on
         and autosuspend_enable() will be called after the display is turned off.
         This mode provides best compatibility for devices using legacy power management
         features such as early suspend / late resume.
         When true, autosuspend_display() and autosuspend_enable() will be called
         independently of whether the display is being turned on or off.  This mode
         enables the power manager to suspend the application processor while the
         display is on.
         This resource should be set to "true" when a doze component has been specified
         to maximize power savings but not all devices support it.
         Refer to autosuspend.h for details.
</string>
<string name="config_powerDecoupleInteractiveModeFromDisplay">
 Power Management: Specifies whether to decouple the interactive state of the
         device from the display on/off state.
         When false, setInteractive(…, true) will be called before the display is turned on
         and setInteractive(…, false) will be called after the display is turned off.
         This mode provides best compatibility for devices that expect the interactive
         state to be tied to the display state.
         When true, setInteractive(…) will be called independently of whether the display
         is being turned on or off.  This mode enables the power manager to reduce
         clocks and disable the touch controller while the display is on.
         This resource should be set to "true" when a doze component has been specified
         to maximize power savings but not all devices support it.
         Refer to power.h for details.
</string>
<string name="config_minimumScreenOffTimeout">
 User activity timeout: Minimum screen off timeout in milliseconds.
         Sets a lower bound for the {@link Settings.System#SCREEN_OFF_TIMEOUT} setting
         which determines how soon the device will go to sleep when there is no
         user activity.
         This value must be greater than zero, otherwise the device will immediately
         fall asleep again as soon as it is awoken.
</string>
<string name="config_maximumScreenDimDuration">
 User activity timeout: Maximum screen dim duration in milliseconds.
         Sets an upper bound for how long the screen will dim before the device goes
         to sleep when there is no user activity.  The dim duration is subtracted from
         the overall screen off timeout to determine the screen dim timeout.
         When the screen dim timeout expires, the screen will dim, shortly thereafter
         the device will go to sleep.
         If the screen off timeout is very short, the dim duration may be reduced
         proportionally.  See config_maximumScreenDimRatio.
         This value may be zero in which case the screen will not dim before the
         device goes to sleep.
</string>
<string name="config_globalActionsKeyTimeout">
 Amount of time in ms the user needs to press the relevant key to bring up the global actions dialog
</string>
<string name="config_maxResolverActivityColumns">
 Maximum number of grid columns permitted in the ResolverActivity
         used for picking activities to handle an intent.
</string>
<string name="config_cellBroadcastAppLinks">
 Set to true to add links to Cell Broadcast app from Settings and MMS app.
</string>
<string name="config_syncstorageengine_masterSyncAutomatically">
 The default value if the SyncStorageEngine should sync automatically or not
</string>
<string name="config_multiuserMaximumUsers">
  Maximum number of supported users
</string>
<string name="config_enableMultiUserUI">
 Whether UI for multi user should be shown
</string>
<string name="config_disableUsbPermissionDialogs">
 If true, then we do not ask user for permission for apps to connect to USB devices.
         Do not set this to true for production devices. Doing so will cause you to fail CTS.
</string>
<string name="config_safe_media_volume_index">
 Safe headphone volume index. When music stream volume is below this index
    the SPL on headphone output is compliant to EN 60950 requirements for portable music
    players.
</string>
<string name="config_mobile_mtu">
 Configure mobile network MTU. The standard default is set here but each carrier
         may have a specific value set in an overlay config.xml file.
</string>
<string name="config_enableWifiDisplay">
 Whether WiFi display is supported by this device.
         There are many prerequisites for this feature to work correctly.
         Here are a few of them:
         * The WiFi radio must support WiFi P2P.
         * The WiFi radio must support concurrent connections to the WiFi display and
           to an access point.
         * The Audio Flinger audio_policy.conf file must specify a rule for the "r_submix"
           remote submix module.  This module is used to record and stream system
           audio output to the WiFi display encoder in the media server.
         * The remote submix module "audio.r_submix.default" must be installed on the device.
         * The device must be provisioned with HDCP keys (for protected content).
</string>
<string name="config_useDevInputEventForAudioJack">
 When true use the linux /dev/input/event subsystem to detect the switch changes
         on the headphone/microphone jack. When false use the older uevent framework.
</string>
<string name="config_safe_media_volume_enabled">
 Whether safe headphone volume is enabled or not (country specific).
</string>
<string name="config_wifiDisplaySupportsProtectedBuffers">
 Set to true if the wifi display supports compositing content stored
         in gralloc protected buffers.  For this to be true, there must exist
         a protected hardware path for surface flinger to composite and send
         protected buffers to the wifi display video encoder.
         If this flag is false, we advise applications not to use protected
         buffers (if possible) when presenting content to a wifi display because
         the content may be blanked.
         This flag controls whether the {@link Display#FLAG_SUPPORTS_PROTECTED_BUFFERS}
         flag is set for wifi displays.
</string>
<string name="config_camera_sound_forced">
 Whether camera shutter sound is forced or not  (country specific).
</string>
<string name="config_dontPreferApn">
 Set to true if we need to not prefer an APN.
         This is being added to enable a simple scenario of pre-paid
         provisioning on some carriers, working around a bug (7305641)
         where if the preferred is used we don\'t try the others.
</string>
<string name="config_restartRadioAfterProvisioning">
 Set to true if after a provisioning apn the radio should be restarted
</string>
<string name="config_requireRadioPowerOffOnSimRefreshReset">
 Boolean indicating if RADIO POWER OFF is required on receiving SIM REFRESH with RESET.
         This will be handled by modem if it is false.
</string>
<string name="config_speed_up_audio_on_mt_calls">
 Flag indicating if the speed up audio on mt call code should be executed
</string>
<string name="config_customAdbPublicKeyConfirmationComponent">
 Name of the activity or service that prompts the user to reject, accept, or whitelist
         an adb host\'s public key, when an unwhitelisted host connects to the local adbd.
         Can be customized for other product types
</string>
<string name="config_customAdbPublicKeyConfirmationSecondaryUserComponent">
 Name of the activity that prompts the secondary user to acknowledge she/he needs to
         switch to the primary user to enable USB debugging.
         Can be customized for other product types
</string>
<string name="config_customVpnConfirmDialogComponent">
 Name of the CustomDialog that is used for VPN
</string>
<string name="config_useFixedVolume">
 Flag indicating that the media framework should not allow changes or mute on any
         stream or master volumes.
</string>
<string name="config_forceDefaultOrientation">
 Flag indicating that this device does not rotate and will always remain in its default
         orientation. Activities that desire to run in a non-compatible orientation will be run
         from an emulated display within the physical display.
</string>
<string name="config_toastDefaultGravity">
 Default Gravity setting for the system Toast view. Equivalent to: Gravity.CENTER_HORIZONTAL | Gravity.BOTTOM
</string>
<string name="config_stkNoAlphaUsrCnf">
 set to false if we need to show user confirmation
         when alpha identifier is not provided by the UICC
</string>
<string name="config_immersive_mode_confirmation_panic">
 Threshold (in ms) under which a screen off / screen on will be considered a reset of the
         immersive mode confirmation prompt.
</string>
<string name="config_valid_wappush_index">
 For some operators, PDU has garbages. To fix it, need to use valid index
</string>
<string name="config_overrideHasPermanentMenuKey">
 Override the default detection behavior for the framework method
         android.view.ViewConfiguration#hasPermanentMenuKey().
         Valid settings are:
         0 - No change. Use the default autodetection behavior.
         1 - The device DOES have a permanent menu key; ignore autodetection.
         2 - The device DOES NOT have a permanent menu key; ignore autodetection.
</string>
<string name="config_hasPermanentDpad">
 Override the DPad detection behavior for configuration purposes
</string>
<string name="config_windowIsRound">
 default window inset isRound property
</string>
<string name="config_windowOutsetBottom">
 Override this value if the device has a chin, i.e. area that is not actual part of the
         screen but you would like to be treated as a real display. The value is the height of the
         chin.
</string>
<string name="config_defaultNetworkScorerPackageName">
 Package name for default network scorer app; overridden by product overlays.
</string>
<string name="config_hasRecents">
 default device has recents property
</string>
<string name="config_windowShowCircularMask">
 default window ShowCircularMask property
</string>
<string name="config_windowEnableCircularEmulatorDisplayOverlay">
 default value for whether circular emulators (ro.emulator.circular)
         should show a display overlay on the screen
</string>
<string name="config_drawLockTimeoutMillis">
 Number of milliseconds to hold a wake lock to ensure that drawing is fully
         flushed to the display while dozing.  This value needs to be large enough
         to account for processing and rendering time plus a frame or two of latency
         in the display pipeline plus some slack just to be sure.
</string>
<string name="skipHoldBeforeMerge">
 Flag indicating apps will skip sending hold request before merge. In this case
        IMS service implementation will do both.i.e.hold followed by merge.
</string>
<string name="useImsAlwaysForEmergencyCall">
 Flag indicating emergency calls will always use IMS irrespective of the state of
    the IMS connection
</string>
<string name="imsServiceAllowTurnOff">
 Flag indicating whether the IMS service can be turned off. If false then
        the service will not be turned-off completely (the ImsManager.turnOffIms() will
        be disabled) but individual Features can be disabled using ImsConfig.setFeatureValue()
</string>
<string name="config_device_volte_available">
 Flag specifying whether VoLTE is available on device
</string>
<string name="config_carrier_volte_available">
 Flag specifying whether VoLTE should be available for carrier: independent of
         carrier provisioning. If false: hard disabled. If true: then depends on carrier
         provisioning, availability etc
</string>
<string name="config_carrier_volte_provisioned">
 Flag specifying whether VoLTE availability is based on provisioning
</string>
<string name="config_carrier_volte_tty_supported">
 Flag specifying whether VoLTE TTY is supported
</string>
<string name="config_device_vt_available">
 Flag specifying whether VT is available on device
</string>
<string name="config_carrier_vt_available">
 Flag specifying whether VT should be available for carrier: independent of
         carrier provisioning. If false: hard disabled. If true: then depends on carrier
         provisioning, availability etc
</string>
<string name="config_device_wfc_ims_available">
 Flag specifying whether WFC over IMS is available on device
</string>
<string name="config_carrier_wfc_ims_available">
 Flag specifying whether WFC over IMS should be available for carrier: independent of
         carrier provisioning. If false: hard disabled. If true: then depends on carrier
         provisioning, availability etc
</string>
    <string name="config_networkSamplingWakesDevice">

</string>
        <string name="config_auto_attach_data_on_creation">

</string>
<string name="config_switch_phone_on_voice_reg_state_change">
 Config determines whether to update phone object when voice registration
         state changes. Voice radio tech change will always trigger an update of
         phone object irrespective of this config
</string>
    <string name="config_sms_force_7bit_encoding">

</string>
<string name="config_LTE_RSRP_threshold_type">
 Flag indicating whether strict threshold is used, or lenient threshold is used,
          when evaluating RSRP for LTE antenna bar display
           0. Strict threshold
           1. Lenient threshold
</string>
<string name="config_zen_repeat_callers_threshold">
 Priority repeat caller threshold, in minutes
</string>
<string name="config_defaultWindowFeatureOptionsPanel">
 Flags enabling default window features. See Window.java
</string>
    <string name="config_defaultWindowFeatureContextMenu">

</string>
        <string name="config_use_sim_language_file">

</string>
<string name="config_LTE_eri_for_network_name">
 Use ERI text for network name on CDMA LTE
</string>
<string name="config_defaultInTouchMode">
 Whether to start in touch mode
</string>
<string name="config_screen_magnification_multi_tap_adjustment">
 Time adjustment, in milliseconds, applied to the default double tap threshold
         used for gesture detection by the screen magnifier.
</string>
<string name="config_enableBurnInProtection">
 If true, the display will be shifted around in ambient mode.
</string>
<string name="config_burnInProtectionMaxRadius">
 Specifies the maximum burn-in offset displacement from the center. If -1, no maximum value
         will be used.
</string>
<string name="config_burnInProtectionMinHorizontalOffset">
 Specifies the minimum burn-in offset horizontally.
</string>
<string name="config_burnInProtectionMaxHorizontalOffset">
 Specifies the maximum burn-in offset horizontally.
</string>
<string name="config_burnInProtectionMinVerticalOffset">
 Specifies the minimum burn-in offset vertically.
</string>
<string name="config_burnInProtectionMaxVerticalOffset">
 Specifies the maximum burn-in offset vertically.
</string>
<string name="config_fingerprintMaxTemplatesPerUser">
 For performance and storage reasons, limit the number of fingerprints per user
</string>
<string name="config_allowAnimationsInLowPowerMode">
 This config is ued to determine whether animations are allowed in low power mode.
</string>
<string name="config_supportDoubleTapWake">
 Whether device supports double tap to wake
</string>
<string name="config_mainBuiltInDisplayIsRound">
 Whether the main built-in display is round. This will affect
         Configuration.screenLayout\'s SCREENLAYOUT_ROUND_MASK flags for Configurations on the
         main built-in display. Change this in device-specific overlays.
         Defaults to the older, deprecated config_windowIsRound already used in
         some existing device-specific resource overlays.
</string>
<string name="config_supportMicNearUltrasound">
 Whether the default microphone audio source supports near-ultrasound frequencies
         (range of 18 - 21 kHz).
</string>
<string name="config_supportSpeakerNearUltrasound">
 Whether the default speaker audio output path supports near-ultrasound frequencies
         (range of 18 - 21 kHz).
</string>
<string name="config_eap_sim_based_auth_supported">
 Flag indicating device support for EAP SIM, AKA, AKA\'
</string>
<string name="config_previousVibrationsDumpLimit">
 How long history of previous vibrations should be kept for the dumpsys.
</string>
<string name="config_mdc_initial_max_retry">
 Set initial MaxRetry value for operators
</string>
<string name="config_cameraLaunchGestureSensorType">
 The OEM specified sensor type for the gesture to launch the camear app.
</string>
<string name="config_cameraDoubleTapPowerGestureEnabled">
 Allow the gesture to double tap the power button twice to start the camera while the device
         is non-interactive.
</string>
</resources>
